{
  "displayName": "dylan",
  "email": "nielsen.dylan@gmail.com",
  "password": "$2a$10$M5C6eAiuVbPQ7kNJN3VOtuaMO47gIH/p86dL7Aa0zCYfHrIVXsKk6",
  "questions": {
        "head": {
            "value": {
                "question": "Lord",
                "dragonAnswer": "Drog",
                "answer": "Drog",
                "attempts": 11,
                "correctAttempts": 5,
                "mValue": 1
            },
            "next": {
                "value": {
                    "question": "Carve",
                    "dragonAnswer": "Dw6rok",
                    "answer": "Dwiirok",
                    "attempts": 5,
                    "correctAttempts": 3,
                    "mValue": 3
                },
                "next": {
                    "value": {
                        "question": "Beautiful",
                        "dragonAnswer": "Brit",
                        "answer": "Brit",
                        "attempts": 10,
                        "correctAttempts": 5,
                        "mValue": 2
                    },
                    "next": {
                        "value": {
                            "question": "Servant",
                            "dragonAnswer": "2r",
                            "answer": "Aar",
                            "attempts": 9,
                            "correctAttempts": 7,
                            "mValue": 3
                        },
                        "next": {
                            "value": {
                                "question": "Hound",
                                "dragonAnswer": "Dok",
                                "answer": "Dok",
                                "attempts": 7,
                                "correctAttempts": 5,
                                "mValue": 4
                            },
                            "next": {
                                "value": {
                                    "question": "Undead",
                                    "dragonAnswer": "D6l",
                                    "answer": "Diil",
                                    "attempts": 8,
                                    "correctAttempts": 4,
                                    "mValue": 5
                                },
                                "next": {
                                    "value": {
                                        "question": "Extinguish",
                                        "dragonAnswer": "Even2r",
                                        "answer": "Evenaar",
                                        "attempts": 0,
                                        "correctAttempts": 0,
                                        "mValue": 1
                                    },
                                    "next": {
                                        "value": {
                                            "question": "Haunt",
                                            "dragonAnswer": "Fol9k",
                                            "answer": "Folook",
                                            "attempts": 0,
                                            "correctAttempts": 0,
                                            "mValue": 1
                                        },
                                        "next": {
                                            "value": {
                                                "question": "Stamina",
                                                "dragonAnswer": "G2n",
                                                "answer": "Gaan",
                                                "attempts": 0,
                                                "correctAttempts": 0,
                                                "mValue": 1
                                            },
                                            "next": {
                                                "value": {
                                                    "question": "Wolf",
                                                    "dragonAnswer": "Groh6k",
                                                    "answer": "Grohiik",
                                                    "attempts": 0,
                                                    "correctAttempts": 0,
                                                    "mValue": 1
                                                },
                                                "next": null
                                            }
                                        }
                                    }
                                }
                            }
                        }
                    }
                }
            }
        }
    }
}
